# BHUMI MANDALIA

## ABOUT ME

I am a GRAPHIC DESIGNER. Currently I am working in DVIO Digital, Pune. I have 3.6 years of experience in Web Designing, Graphic Design, UI Design, banner design, Print Ads, Digital Marketing. I'm looking for suitable opening in designing where I can explore my skill.

## **EDUCATION**

Completed High School in 2010 from Manikrupa highschool, Ahmedabad.
Completed B.E.(Computer Engineering) in 2014 from GEC, Gandhinagar.

## **EXPERIENCE**

7i Webtech (Feb, 2016 - Dec, 2016)
I have worked on Website Design, Image Editing, Banner.

Rubiksweb Technology (Jan, 2017 - July, 2017)
I have worked on Website design, App design, Logo,
Flyer, Banner, Image editing.

Hikebranding (Aug, 2017 - March 2019)
I have worked on Website design, Logo, Flyer, Banner,
Image editing, Brouchers.

Dvio Digital pvt.lmt.(March 2019 - Till now)
I have worked on Digital Marketing, Flyer, Emailers,
Banner, Posters, Brouchers, Print Ads.

## SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Corel Draw

# DESIGNER ABILITIES

Web design, Graphic design, Digital Marketing, App design, User interface, Print ads, Posters Branding, Brochure, Infographic, Emailers.

# CONTACT

#### **ADDRESS**

B2/12, Raagdari apartment, DP road, Aundh, Pune.

#### **EMAIL ADDRESS**

bhumi009g5@gmail.com

#### MOBILE NO.

7990239592